No identification with actual persons , companies ,
and organizations is intended or should be inferred .
Finally , the 4th floor .
I 'm freaking nervous !
What the hell ! So scared .
That 's scary ...
Damn it ! Don 't play around !
You little chicken .
402 ...
Isn 't this it ? 402 ?
It really exists .
This shit is heavy .
Hey , Hae-Chan . You said we wouldn 't come .
But we 're right in front of room 402 .
You see ? 402 !
We 're not chicken like you .
We 're real men !
Now we 'll unlock it and leave .
You thought we cannot make it .
But we made it !
We 're real men , you sucker !
We 're opening the door !
Hold this for me .
We 're doing it for real !
But it doesn 't go through .
Stop acting !
It 's not opening . I don 't know how ...
Total wuss .
- What 's was that ? - What ?
Wait .
" HORROR TIM ES "
Hello , everyone .
You must 've seen this on Youtube .
The high schoolers who went missing at Gonjiam .
So what should I do ?
I checked whether the clip was fabricated .
Ta-da !
Teenage boys went missing on their horror experience
That 's real .
And the ghost picture doesn 't seem fake .
So !
Our next stop for Horror Times ' 3rd horror experience squad is
one of three most haunted houses in Korea
and one of 7 freakiest places on earth !
Namyoung Psychiatric Hospital .
Since it opened in May 1961
it was the best mental hospital in Korea
but it closed in October 1979
after a mass suicide of patients
and the disappearance of its director .
The building still stands , yet abandoned .
Gonjiam asylum , folks !
Footages !
No. 1 026
The 11 Th 5 . 16 citizens award ceremony was held at the Blue House .
The grand prize goes to Park Young-ae
the director of Namyoung Psychiatric Hospital
recognizing her achievement
for treating not only mental patients ,
but also political prisoners and brutal criminals .
There are numerous rumors around Gonjiam asylum .
Some say it was built on the place
where the Japanese brutally murdered
and buried the Korean resistance
so that nobody could trace the bodies .
Or it was the national torturing facility
in the 60s and 70s disguised as asylum
or that the mass suicide was actually
murdered by the director
who then killed herself , not went missing .
So there are countless reports of ghost sightings
and hearings of wailing after the closure of the asylum .
The biggest rumor among all is about room 402 ,
the only locked space of the asylum .
They say whoever dares to open that room is cursed to death .
So we , the Horror Times are going to the Gonjiam asylum ,
on October 26th the day it closed ,
to investigate the truth
about supernatural phenomena
and the ghosts many people witnessed .
Care to join ?
I 'm at the terrace of a cafe at Gangnam .
Guess I 'm the first one . Let me wait for others to come .
- For Horror Times ? - Yes .
- Hello . - Hi .
- Are you filming me ? - Yes .
Yes , my family is in the States
and I 'm here with my dance crew .
Awesome .
What do you do ?
Studying nursing ...
Boys must like you !
I 'm at a women 's univ .
Isn 't he the one ?
Here they are !
Hello , everyone .
Hello .
- Nice to see you . - Hello .
Let 's do some introduction .
Sure !
These are the selected applicants
Oh Ah-yeon , Park Ji-hyun and ...
- Charlotte ! - Charlotte Moon .
And from Horror Times ,
Lee Seung-wook , Park Sung-Hun .
- Hello . - Hello .
Seung-wook will do MC
and Sung-Hun will operate the 1 st camera .
And you know who I am ?
Ha-joon , the captain of the squad .
- It 's like a group date . - Right .
- Didn 't mean it ... - Just stop talking .
Seems like one is missing .
- As if you saw a ghost ... - Isn 't he ?
I guess so .
- Shall we call him ? - Here !
- Here ! - Come here !
Yes , please come here !
Here he comes !
Hello , you 're here for Horror Times ?
- Hello ! - Sorry , I was lost nearby .
Je-yoon will do editing and graphic effects .
Ji-hyun , 2nd camera .
One go pro camera per two .
Please memorize the floor plan
and the cue-sheet .
What are you doing ?
It 's for the fuck-you-mentary .
- Cheers ! - Bottoms up !
- Nice to meet you ! - Cheers !
Where have you been to among CNN 's 7 freakiest places ?
Sedlec Ossuary in Czech ,
the Island of the Dolls in Mexico ,
and Aokigahara Forest in Japan .
I 've been to three places .
Everyone who 's seen the ghost at Gonjiam
heard some sound first .
- You mean a ping pong ball ? - You 're right .
People who saw the ghosts there heard a ping pong ball .
But why that specific sound ?
Actually there is a ping pong table .
Broken in half .
Can 't it be the echoed sound
of water drops ?
But why did the director kill all her patients ?
There 's no proof she killed them .
People say that as all the patients died
and the director went missing .
Rumor also says she hung herself at the hospital 's bathroom .
Her neck apparently was stretched a foot long .
Gross ...
Are you scared ?
Me ?
No .
- You seem to be . - No way !
Whose idea is it to air this live ?
A car racing club uploaded
the clip of their wild speed racing
on their website a while ago .
It reached 200K views and earned more than 1 00K for ads .
- 1 00K dollars ? - Yes .
Can you earn money airing this kind of stuff ?
Hell yes ...
I guess you are a kind of student
who learns everything by the book ...
Never breaks rules .
- She 's cute . - Yes , very cute but ...
- learning everything by the book . - Stop it .
Not by experiences ...
How many views are you expecting ?
- A million ! - A million ?
I am aiming for that .
- Heavy . - Do you mean a million ?
It means we 'll earn $ 500K as it 's 5 times of 200K views ?
Captain .
I really think we should send her home .
Why ?
- Ready ? - Sure .
Oh my god !
- Did he catch it ? - I can 't believe it !
He caught it !
Unbelievable !
- He got it ! Right ? - Let me see !
Impossible !
How you do that ?
Hurry !
Just throw it !
Shoot it !
Hey !
Oh my gosh , I 'm so sorry .
I think we really should send her home .
- You come here . - Please ...
For million views !
Million views !
Cheers !
No one saw the director ghost .
Don 't you think her spirit should be there , too ?
You 're right .
But people only saw the patients and a high school girl .
Patients I get it .
But why a high school girl ?
About 30 years ago ?
Three high school girls went there to test their nerves
and were found unconscious while trying
to open room 402 .
They were immediately sent to the hospital .
Two of them went insane
and jumped to their deaths .
The other one remained unconscious .
That 's what I heard .
That 's why there 's a rumor
That the room 402 is cursed .
What 's our plan for room 402 then ?
The climax of this experience will be opening the door .
What ?
- You never mentioned that . - Great !
It 's more fun to know by surprise .
- We 're opening it ! - Yeah !
- Not all of us are coming in ? - Why ?
Are you scared ?
Hell , no !
You 're really good at joking .
Seriously , who is opening that door ?
Guys ready ? Let 's do this !
Go , go , go !
- No ! - Pass me , please !
No , hell no !
You 've got it !
Wait , wait .
- Go Je-yoon , go Je-yoon ! - I can 't accept it .
- Someone manipulated it . - What is he saying ?
Horror Times don 't do such thing !
Something 's wrong with it .
Are you scared ? I can go with you .
You take care of yourself .
Why is he shaking ?
He 's relieved .
He saw us !
Wait for me !
Wait !
Yeah come on !
Let 's go now .
Impressive .
- Can that follow us ? - Of course !
We can 't get in anyway if we get there early .
Let 's have some fun .
You mean going for a dip like previous horror experience ?
It 's almost November .
You 've reached the destination .
There .
That 's the entrance all barricaded .
They blocked it !
We can 't get in through here .
Then how can we go through ?
We 'll get in from the back .
Police patrol here even at night .
- Really ? - Yes .
Look at that .
This car can get in ?
It 's heavy .
It 's scary here .
- We 're here . - Let 's get out .
Finally !
- It must be heavy . - You 're not helping ?
Hey , look at the camera .
This way .
We are going all the way to the top ?
Yes .
The hospital is right in front of us .
Why should we climb this hill ?
There are surveillance cameras .
I have a headach .
Can 't you see these ?
Why you wearing heals ?
Je-yoon , come on !
Hey , hurry up !
Je-yoon !
Are you okay ?
Is this a horror club
or an extreme sports club ?
A drone camera is following us from above .
Hello !
Let 's go .
Do it properly !
- Help me with this . - What ?
So cozy .
It is 9 : 25 PM .
Sung-Hun and Seung-wook
are out to Gonjiam Asylum
installing CCTV inside .
Wish they wouldn 't encounter the ghosts too early .
We have ghosts here , too .
My hat !
The camera is on .
O. K. , they 're inside .
Seung-wook , that 's good .
Okay with angles and positions .
Wow . No jokes .
The camera moved automatically just now .
This is a follow cam . The camera follows movement .
Everything is new to you , kiddo .
- She 's so cute . - We should send her home .
Sung-Hun ! Seung-wook !
Good job !
It 's freezing when it gets dark .
Hurry . The tent is warm .
How was Gonjiam ?
It 's there ...
Good job . Did you see the ghost ?
They are not there yet .
I 'm so hungry .
- Good job . - Really .
I 'm starving . We should eat something .
- Sweetie ! - I 'm making noodles now .
Good girl . You 're smart in that sense .
- You 're making it now ? - Yes .
- Let 's eat . - It 's done .
- Tuck in . - Do We have a ladle ?
It 's good .
Are you okay ?
Water , please .
No , I 'm not .
- Wow , GoPro sessions ! - Dope !
- So many of them ! - Are we bringing them all in ?
Of course .
What is this ?
Electro-magnetic field meter
What 's in Korean ?
A ghost detector .
An electro-magnetic field tester to be exact .
The special magnetic field flows
where psychotic flow occurs .
So people use this to detect spirits .
We usually call this EMF meter .
It fits there .
I 'm fixing it in case you take it off
when you get too scared .
You can only release it here .
It makes me more nervous .
Tighter , tighter !
Tighter .
Yes , tighter !
With this , you can record your face and your POV at the same time .
See ?
Dope !
- Cool ? - Yes .
So it 's almost working hours for the ghosts .
Everyone must be nervous .
Shall we head down ?
Go , go , go , go , go . Let 's go !
- Yes ! - Let 's Go !
Check Ah-yeon 's face cam
and Je-yoon 's POV cam .
I don 't receive them .
And now ?
It 's okay . Sound check .
Say your name .
Sung-Hun .
Seung-wook .
Charlotte .
Ji-hyun .
Je-yoon !
Ah-yeon .
Sound check done .
Hey .
I already feel a chill .
- Something might come out . - Right ?
Shall we use the EM F ?
Already ? We 're not even near the entrance .
Why , why ?
- Something just passed . - I heard a flap .
- Was it a bird ? - Bird ?
That freaked me out .
Damn it .
Be still , my heart .
It 's just it came out so suddenly .
I 'm not afraid of anything .
- You look so chicken-hearted . - No .
- You 're lying . - I 'm not !
Don 't lie .
Why are you laughing ?
- What 's this ? - What the Fuck .
What ?
- What is it ? - What is it ?
Tell us !
Don 't touch it .
What happened exactly ?
Leave it there . We can use it as a mark .
- Right . - Good idea .
Someone 's underwear as a mark ...
We 've over 12,000 views .
We 'll start to air in 5 mins .
Careful .
Be careful .
Watch your steps .
Why you wearing heals ?
- Be careful ! - Whew .
Ji-hyun , okay ?
Watch out !
Shhh , give me your hand , Ah-yeon .
It 's slippery here .
Watch out , Charlotte .
Thank you .
Look there .
Dope .
Damn it .
So the top floor is the 4th ?
Yes , the basement is the first floor here .
Where is room 402 ?
I can 't tell from outside .
Rumor says if you take a shit there , you can make it big .
You should 've told me earlier ! I already took a shit !
Damn it .
Let 's go !
Hurry .
Be careful .
Why ?
Turn off your lights , everyone !
Cover LED lights !
- Cover them . - Why ?
It 's not the patrol time .
Is it a cop ?
Be quiet and wait .
Are they gone ?
This place is crazy .
What are you doing , Ji-hyun ?
- Come here . - I 'm coming .
- Let 's move together . - It 's so scary .
I 'm scared .
Look !
This is the main entrance leading to the 2nd floor .
Let 's get in .
Go ahead .
Wait for me . It 's scary .
Aren 't you coming ?
Need to shoot from behind .
Okay .
Wanna leak .
I 'm shooting . You go ahead .
I 'll shoot from behind .
Got it .
- Shall we go on ? - Yes .
Crap , what shall I do ? Is it for real ?
It 's really terrifying .
What 's written on it ?
' Enter and you will die . '
And ' Fuck it ' , afterwards ...
Time to start airing .
Hey , gather here . We 're starting !
Okay !
Stand by .
Three , Two , One .
Go !
We , Horror Times ' horror experience squad
managed to sneak into the prohibited Gonjiam asylum .
Today is Oct. 26th . And it just passed midnight .
We can already get the chill in this building
where the spirits are said to appear midnight .
Korea 's first live horror show ever !
Gonjiam horror experience
begins now !
Very good opening , Seung-wook .
VR first and get in !
- Hurry , hurry ! - Let 's go !
Music !
- Enter . - Enter .
Seung-wook , stand by .
Go !
It is four past midnight .
We 're finally inside of Gonjiam asylum .
Here 's the lobby .
' Someone 's living here ... '
I 'm getting a chill .
You always get the chill .
What do you want me to get ? Chocked ?
Hang on .
Here 's the hallway on the 2nd floor .
The rooms are lined on both sides .
There are lots of garbage on the floor .
We 're approaching the reception desk .
Ji-hyun and Charlotte , you go ahead .
Damn ...
Where is it ? It 's here .
Here .
Ji-hyun , stand by . Go !
Charlotte pours holy water
she took from Myung-dong Cathedral into a bowl .
We 're going to put a camera
and capture ghosts .
Seung-wook , your line .
We already set up the high-tech equipments
at the spots of supernatural phenomena and ghost appearance .
Let me brief you the rundown of ...
What is it ?
Where ?
Where is it ?
Was it the director 's room ?
It closed by itself . Didn 't it ?
This is real , everyone .
The door of the director 's room got closed by itself .
We will go and check .
I 'm horrified .
" DI RECTOR 'S ROOM "
We 're now in the director 's room .
Might be a coincidence but
just before , the door got closed by itself .
It 's the phenomenon many people
who came here witnessed .
Look at this !
- What ? - Come here , hurry !
Sung-Hun , zoom in the picture .
Seung-wook , your line .
Seems like a group photo
of the patients and hospital crews .
It looks like an ordinary group photo
but if you take a closer look , something is off .
All staring at ...
Different directions ...
And the woman in the center seems to be
the director who is rumored to
kill all the patients and disappear .
- She looks creepy . - I agree .
We found other pictures .
Director getting the award .
Her playing ping pong .
Guess this lady was fond of ping pong .
That can explain the sound of ping pong ball .
Stop it ! You scare me !
What is it ? Over there ...
It reads ' The people who read . '
Seems like she read some books back then .
- From President Park Jung-hee . - That 's a surprise !
By the way , who 's Park Jung-hee ?
Ex-president .
Ex-president , Father of the very former one .
Was her father a president , too ?
Charlotte ...
What the hell ?
I was so surprised ...
This really freaks out .
Is that hair ?
- Not a person ? - No .
Let 's wrap it up .
Luckily we 've found some pictures
and shown them to you .
I and Sung-Hun are going to prepare
the mediumistic ritual to bring out the revengeful spirits
of the patients who were unfairly killed .
Meanwhile , other members
will introduce you the horror spots
on the 1 st , 3rd and 4th floors .
Everything will be live , of course .
O. K !
Everyone , move to the spots and stand by
While I 'm playing the replay .
For supernatural phenomena and ghosts ' appearance .
Let me brief you the rundown of ...
Charlotte and Ji-hyun on the 1 st floor , ready ?
Yeap !
Time for the horror spots .
Ready , go !
I am on the 1 st floor now .
And Charlotte who 's already experienced
3 among CNN 's 7 freakiest places
is leaving her signature to celebrate her 4th experience .
Charlotte ?
Hello , everyone !
After Sedlec Ossuary in Czech ,
Aokigahara Forest in Japan
and the Island of the Dolls in Mexico ,
among CNN 's 7 freakiest places ,
I , Charlotte finally arrived at Gonjiam asylum !
I left my signature as a token
just like the other places .
And I can see someone wrote ' Let 's live ' here .
Oh , Scary .
Move to the corridor .
' Someone lives here ' , it says .
What ?
No , it says it 's ghosts living here .
Damn . Ghosts live here , everyone .
And we are at the place where ghosts live .
And there are weird writings on the wall .
Ji-hyun . Look at this .
Why is this turning off ?
" LABORATORY "
This is the lab , everyone .
Let 's go in .
What the heck ?
The inside seems like the lab .
Water on the floor .
The water is leaking .
Numerous medical charts scattered on the floor .
Burnt trace on the wall , too .
Cabinets are collapsed on the floor .
Here is the laboratory .
There are tiles on the walls ,
and most of them are shattered
as if the room was bombed .
On the floor , there are IVs , needles ...
and a microscope .
Also there are lots of medicine bottles .
And a doll , too .
Ji-hyun !
It 's the spot my friend took the psychic picture .
Check it out .
Here 's the spot where my friend took the picture
when she came here last year .
It was real .
Point the camera at me .
Are you okay ?
- What is it ? - What the hell ? !
- What is that smell ? - Oh my ...
Is that a chicken ?
Let 's go out . We will leave here first .
Good job , you two .
Move to the 4th floor .
Je-yoon and Ah-yeon on the 3rd floor .
Stand by and go !
Welcome back .
Ah-yeon and I are in the hallway of the 3rd floor .
We are only one floor upper
but it feels colder here .
We will check the temperature . Ah-yeon ?
It 's 13 Celsius .
13 Celsius .
It 's 13 Celsius on the 3rd floor .
What about the 2nd floor earlier ?
13 Celsius .
... The temperature is the same .
But there 's a thing called sensory temperature .
The sensory temperature I feel on the 3rd floor right now
It is about minus 13 Celsius .
There 's a ping pong table !
There really is a ping pong table as rumor says it .
There 's a dead bird .
Je-yoon , calm down a bit .
Okay .
What now ?
Introduction of the 3rd floor !
Right , we 'll now show you the rooms on the 3rd floor .
You must know well too ,
umm , people who 've been here
often said they witnessed
supernatural phenomena on the 1 st and 2nd floors
and actual ghosts here on this floor and the 4th floor .
They are said to be haunted spirits of patients wrongly killed .
We will now ... check out these rooms .
What the ...
Je-yoon , your line .
Alright .
This is the shower room where
the ghosts were seen many times .
You can see on that wall inside
an old stain in shape of a person .
Please zoom onto it , Ah-yeon .
It does look like a person .
That is a so-called ' ghost spot ' .
That we don 't want to believe ...
Anyway we , horror experience squad ,
installed this follow cam and a go pro
on this highest spot to confirm
the existence of the ghost .
Now we 're finally going further into the bathing room .
Here we are .
I can see ...
There ! That !
What is it ? What 's that ?
Damn it ! What is it ?
Holy ...
It 's a wig .
Shit , put that away !
It 's so freaking scary ! Put it away .
I said put that away ! Don 't do that !
Don 't ! Damn it !
Don 't do it ! I warned you !
- You damn ... - Why is it here ?
Somebody must 've left it for a joke .
Don 't do that ! I warned you !
I 'm serious ! You think I 'm kidding ?
That 's it for the 3rd floor ...
Ji-hyun and Charlotte on the 4th , stand by .
This is the hallway of 4th floor
the top ghost spot in the asylum .
Here are our state-of-the-art equipment to trace the ghosts .
The ceiling is equipped with
6 flash lights with infrared censor
responding to a slightest movement
and the minimum energy .
We will now only have to wait until the ghost is spotted .
Now to Ji-hyun .
This is the climax of horror experience ,
the infamous room 402
where no one has been in since the closure of the hospital .
The room used to be the intensive care room .
So many people challenging Gonjiam asylum tried to open
this door which has been closed for so long .
But every single one of them failed
and were said to either have committed strange suicides ,
fallen in comas or died in accidents .
So people call it as the curse of room 402 .
We tried to see with our eyes
if it never opens .
No , I can 't open it .
Did you all see it ?
The door is closed as a solid rock .
But ! Later ,
we 'll be the first ones to open
and shoot inside of room 402 .
We 'll get to the bottom of the mystery of this room .
Coming soon .
Okay , great !
55,000 views .
COLLECTIVE CARE ROOM , 1 ST FLOOR
CORRIDOR , 2ND FLOOR
SUPPLY ROOM , 3RD FLOOR
SHOWER ROOM , 3RD FLOOR
BATH ING ROOM , 3RD FLOOR
ROOM 402
You will wait here until I finish shooting the intro
and follow me while I go around the room .
Make sure to shoot at your positions
in any cases during the ritual .
Okay .
Let 's begin the ritual .
Music is ... on .
Seung-wook , your turn .
Now I am in the director 's room
the place for our mediumistic ritual .
Can you see these ?
The red strings attached with small bells
are hanging like a spider web .
Amulet , millet , and cinnabar
are prepared on the table for the ritual .
Now !
We will perform the dangerous ritual to call out the ghosts .
I 'd leave this room this minute
if it were not for the live broadcasting .
I 'm that much scared and nervous , but !
We will keep our promise
to broadcast this ritual all live .
Ah-yeon , the youngest member , will conduct the ritual .
Ah-yeon , let 's begin .
She puts light on the incense
and burns the amulet
filled with spell calling out the haunted spirits .
A monk at Bomoon Temple generously offered us the amulet .
Get up and put your hands together .
Now we will sit together and wait to see
what happens ...
The candle light is flickering .
What is it ?
What the heck ?
- Damn it ! - What the hell is it ?
What ? What ? What 's going on ?
To where !
Jesus Christ ...
Did you all see the surveillance camera turned ?
It is not a joke !
The rumors were all true !
Did you all shoot it ?
I missed it completely .
This place is of another level .
Don 't scare me .
Comment , Seung-wook !
Put everyone in the frame , Sung-Hun .
Stand by , go !
Did you all see that ? I still can 't believe my own eyes .
The place is closed off
from outside .
But soon after the ritual began
the candle , the bells
and the camera moved by itself .
As if someone 's not happy about our challenge .
But we promise you that we 'll finish our mission
whatever risk lies ahead of us .
Don 't go anywhere .
Okay !
Move to the next spot .
I 'll air the replay .
She puts light on the incense ...
- Yes , captain . - They didn 't notice , did they ?
No , they absolutely freaked out .
Did it look real ?
Sure . It rocked !
What is the number now ?
1 00K views !
- 1 00K , really ? - Unbelievable !
We 've got the good start ,
so we need to do it right to reach 1 million views .
Double-check the settings and lead their reactions .
Got it !
I think Charlotte 's reactions are killing it .
I 'll try to incite her more .
Good . Make sure that they 'd not find out .
Even a ghost cannot . Gotta go .
What the hell !
You 're kidding me ?
What ...
Come on .
Perfect . Perfect timing .
What now ?
So we are now in the lab
on the 1 st floor after the ritual .
We 're a bit eased but like all of you watching online
we still can 't figure out how to explain what 's just happened .
Anyway we 'll stick to our plan and go into the lab .
Well ...
The entire room smells weird .
- This is the lab ? - It 's further inside .
Isn 't it dope ?
This is the inside of the lab .
That 's the stench .
I broke a glass bottle before .
On the floor , left side . Can you see ?
Something like a dead chicken . That 's what stinks .
Hold on . Why is there a doll
in the lab room ?
Are you kidding ?
It wasn 't there before . Right , Ji-hyun ?
It was in the cabinet , not there .
What ?
The doll was in the cabinet !
Zoom in onto the doll .
Looks like the doll in the picture . A patient was holding it .
Shit .
No way .
Is someone else here ?
What are you doing ?
What are you doing ? Don 't touch it .
No ! Don 't touch it ! Put it back !
Put it down ! Lee Seung-wook !
Hey , put it down now !
Right now ! Put it down !
- Seung-wook . - Shoot this , quick !
Can 't you just put it down ?
Charlotte !
Je-yoon , follow her .
Captain , check it out !
Yes . That 's the same doll .
Captain said it 's the same one . Why is he touching it ?
Charlotte , calm down .
You just can 't randomly touch things in places like this .
Ji-hyun ! You saw it too .
The doll was in the cabinet !
Are we the only people in here ?
I will put the picture on screen ,
your comment , Seung-wook .
Stand by , go !
You see this doll I 'm holding ?
Don 't be shocked .
This doll which Charlotte claims was in the cabinet
is the doll from the picture in the director 's room
where we performed the ritual .
Please compare them .
Why has this
doll shown up
and has it moved itself ?
Is there really a supernatural energy in this place ?
Strange things keep happening here . It 's all real
and you 're watching all live !
Good , we 'll be back soon ...
You 're fucking natural born actors !
I can 't stay here . I want to leave .
Charlotte , how can we leave ?
This is really weird .
We can 't just leave .
Yeah , Charlotte .
Stop shooting , Ah-yeon .
- I 'm sorry , Charlotte . - You too , stop shooting !
Lee Seung-wook !
You never touch things in places like this !
They 're cursed !
You can be in a serious trouble !
Sorry .
I just wanted to check as I couldn 't believe my eyes .
Damn it ...
We should give her some time ...
It 's more dangerous to be on her own .
Let 's just finish up and get out of here , okay ?
Do you all hear me ?
If everyone wants to quit here ,
I will follow your decision .
Then all we have done so far would turn into nothing .
Let 's hang in there a bit , shall we ?
Wrap this up as safely as possible just as Charlotte said .
Yes , we are here together , so let 's finish this together .
Okay then .
Hey , you never do anything risky !
Yes , ma 'am . I won 't touch a thing !
I am so sorry .
- Never ! I mean it . - Alright , I got it .
It 's a break .
Let 's move to the next spot and stand by .
Je-yoon and Ah-yeon , go to the 4th floor .
You 'll be on air soon .
Install the infrared flashes on the ceiling .
Yes , captain .
Can we take a minute ?
When the 1 st floor is done ,
we 'll be go short on the 3rd and 4th .
Seung-wook and Sung-Hun , let me know when you 're ready .
- Alright . - Sure .
Can we just take a minute ? Please ?
- Don 't do that again , ever ! - I got it !
- Can 't you hear me ? - Let 's move !
Are you alright , Charlotte ?
- Yeah . - Let 's go .
Everyone , stand by and ...
This is the collective care room .
Take a look inside .
The ceiling has fallen in
and small wooden closets surround the walls .
It looks like a catacomb
bombarded during the war .
The patients were given so-called treatments
in these small wooden closets .
So creepy .
Well , I will look into this coffin with a door .
Strangely , there 's a hole
on the chest level , not on the face .
What was this hole for ?
Not for the surveillance , I guess .
Let me open the door .
There 's no knob .
Why ? What 's wrong ?
- Shit . - Why ?
Someone pulled my arm .
Stop messing around , I warned you !
I 'm not kidding !
I told you ! This place is fucking cursed !
Seung-wook , put in your hand .
Sung-Hun , shake the camera more .
Seung-wook , your line .
Someone did pull my arm inside that door .
I can 't tell exactly ' cause it happened too fast .
So I will put my arm in there again .
- Are you insane ? - Don 't do it !
Stop him !
- Don 't do it ! Please don 't ! - Why not !
Let me do it !
Hey , don 't !
- It 's too dangerous ! - Stop her right now ! Quick !
Okay , alright . I got it !
Take this .
No !
Nothing ...
Ji-hyun ! Ji-hyun !
- What is going on ? - Captain !
- What is it ? - Do something ! Ji-hyun !
Ji-hyun , your arm ...
They scream like they riding the pirate ship .
- I hear the ping pong ball ! - Get the EM F out .
It was written ' Let 's live ' but
changed into ' Let 's die ' !
Are you sure ?
This place is cursed .
We have to leave ... or we are all gonna die .
Let 's leave , Charlotte .
I can 't be here any longer .
- What are you doing ? - We are leaving .
- Hey , Ji-hyun . - Look at this .
We never know what comes next .
We 're cursed . What shall I do ?
- Hey ... - Move away , will you ?
Captain ! You hear us ?
- Calm down . - You saw it too !
You saw what happened at the mediumistic ritual .
It even pulled my scarf , too .
And it grabbed your arm too like it did to mine .
And the letters on the wall changed !
Listen , Ji-hyun ... the truth is ... at the ritual ...
Hey ! We 're scared too . We 're frightened but ...
we 're on board together so let 's finish and leave together .
Even captain doesn 't know what to say !
If any shit happens , who will take care of that ?
Move ! We 're leaving . Let 's go .
Be careful Charlotte .
I can see someone wrote ' Let 's Live ' here .
Hey bro !
Bro !
Ha-joon !
Say something !
Yes , Seung-wook .
Why didn 't you say anything !
The connection is bad .
Ji-hyun and Charlotte left .
I know . I saw .
I checked the letters on the wall .
Did they change ?
Are you kidding ? No way .
It was ' let 's die ' from the beginning .
I 'm just speechless .
Then what is wrong with them ?
Don 't know. they 're just freaking out
Charlotte was already panicking
since you touched the doll in the lab .
But you just saw it , too .
Ji-hyun 's arm pulled and Charlotte 's scarf , too .
It seemed like Ji-hyun was faking .
She seemed to figure about our show .
Why the hell would she fake it ?
How should I know ? Maybe she just wanted to leave ?
- Then the scar on her arm ? - Right .
There might have been thorns inside .
How about Charlotte ?
I saw her scarf with my own eyes !
I filmed it too !
That 's what I find strange , too
so I keep checking the video .
Was there any wind blowing in ?
It 's fucking closed underground !
How could the wind blow in ?
There must be something .
Freaking strange . Let 's stop here .
You think you can fucking end like this ?
Listen carefully . We have to finish this .
Do you know how many are the views now ?
More than 300K !
What if we stop now ?
No ad for the halted broadcasting !
Let 's try just little more .
A brief tour on the 3nd floor and open room 402
and it 's a wrap .
What if something happens !
I will buy some time playing a short replay ...
- Let 's go live again . - Screw it !
Seung-wook ... Lee Seung-wook !
Come back !
Hey you !
Damn it !
I shouldn 't have signed on the wall .
I 'm cursed and might actually die .
That 's why we left . It should be okay .
- You saw it too . - Charlotte !
Under my name , it 's written ...
I said we 'd be okay !
What should I do ?
Get up !
Charlotte .
We go back to the base camp now
and can go home in the morning .
Let 's go home .
We can go home .
Home ...
Let 's go home .
We can go home .
You see ?
The scarf is pulled up by itself .
It 's not the wind .
Let 's get out of here with Je-yoon and Ah-yeon .
- Bro . - Yeah .
Hey , let 's make a deal .
What ?
If we end here everything becomes useless .
300K view can earn $ 150K for ads .
Let 's ask for 30 % more
we can get at least $ 40K each .
Continue this ?
As if someone 's not happy ...
Ji-hyun ...
Je-yoon ,
Seung-wook and Ah-yeon ...
Charlotte and Sung-hoon , all six are there .
Who the hell shot this then ?
What the heck ! No !
No , don 't do this to me !
No !
No way !
Damn it !
As if someone 's not happy ...
Ha-joon .
Yeah .
We have some conditions .
What conditions ?
Raise our shares by 20 % each . Then we 're in .
And for the others , too .
What do you say ?
Okay for 20 % more for you and the others , too .
We 're going back live when the replay is done .
Hurry to the 3rd floor .
Don 't ever cut the radio again .
Or I will kill you .
Was it this far ?
It 's taking too long .
Look at that !
We 're right on track .
We put it there on the way .
We 're almost there .
Almost there . Let 's go .
" SHOWER ROOM "
What you see is the shower room
one of the top two ghost spots
along with the hallway of 4th floor
in this asylum .
Looking up ,
you can see the follow cams .
But no particular signs so far .
What is this sound ?
Is it from supply room ?
Leave the shower room , move to the supply room !
Both of you , fast !
Seung-wook , your line .
We just heard strange sound coming from here ,
the supply room .
You must 've heard it , too .
A loud sound of something
being crashed against the wall .
What was the sound ?
Sung-Hun , go behind the cabinet and shoot it !
Seung-wook , say something first !
Bro !
Say it !
Did you all see that ?
What if there 's ...
the supernatural energy ...
Sung-Hun !
Seung-wook !
Lee Seung-wook !
Hey !
Wake up !
Seung-wook , please !
Why ?
How ...
How is it possible ?
We already passed by it .
This place is weird , too . Ji-hyun ...
Hold on .
What 's this smell ?
Why is it here ?
These were at the lab !
Ji-hyun !
What is wrong with you ?
No , don 't do that !
Ji-hyun ...
Oh my god ...
Captain ! Captain ...
Where are you ?
Ji-hyun ...
Please help me ...
Save me ...
No ! Help me ! Please !
Please let me out !
Open the door !
Sung-Hun ...
We have to leave right now !
Let 's go now ! Fast !
The door is almost opened !
That doesn 't matter .
We shouldn 't be here . We have to leave !
Why ?
Seung-wook is locked in the room downstairs .
Fuck that bastard ! We 're about to reach one million !
What are you talking about ?
We must not be here .
We have to save Seung-wook and get out of this place !
- Yes , captain . - Ah-yeon .
Open the door and get in now .
Captain told me to open the door and get in now .
You two listen to me .
The ritual and the doll ,
we staged them .
What ?
We faked it for the views !
But everything going on right now is real !
That fucking moron ...
Seung-wook might die . We have to save him now !
Is this for real ?
I mean it ! We 're all going to die if we stay !
If you don 't do it , I 'll do it myself .
The ping-pong ball again !
Shit ! What the hell is that ?
What ...
Is someone inside ?
What 's going on ?
Everything is real .
Please help me !
Save me !
Charlotte ?
Is that you ?
- I can 't open the door ! - Let me do it . Charlotte !
- Charlotte ! - Do something ! Charlotte !
What shall we do ?
- Charlotte ! - Charlotte !
Sung-Hun !
- Where are you going ?
Sung-Hun ! Sung-Hun !
Je-yoon ...
- Sung Hun ! - Sung-Hun !
What 's going on ?
What the fuck is this ?
- Ah-yeon ... - I 'm here .
Where 's Sung-Hun ?
Don 't move .
What is it under our feet ?
It feels like water .
You have the light ?
What is wrong with it ?
- Why isn 't it working ? - Shit .
Why is it echoing in here ?
I guess we are ...
- in room 402 . - What ?
You got the camcorder , right ?
Give me that .
What ?
Where are we ?
There 's no door here .
Why is there no door ?
Water ?
How is it possible ?
What 's going on ?
There 's someone .
Where ?
- A girl ... - No way .
Is looking down on us .
Are we really in room 402 ?
Je-yoon ...
On your face ! The hands !
You too , Ah-yeon ...
Don 't do that ...
Someone 's here ...
We have to get out of here .
Ah-yeon ... Ah-yeon !
Sung-Hun ...
Ah-yeon ...
Je-yoon !
Sung-Hun !
Can you hear me ?
Please help me ! Where are you ?
Help me , please !
Save me ! Sung-Hun !
Please come help me !
" It 's not a live broadcast ? "
" It 's cut off after it turns out a fake show . "
" I knew they would manipulate it . "
" ONJ IAM : HAUNTED ASYLUM "
Directed by JUNG Bum-shik
The story , all names , characters , and incidents
portrayed in this production are fictitious .
No identification with actual persons ( living or deceased ) ,
companies , organizations , and products is intended or should be inferred .
Subtitles translated by Cherry Cheng and Kassidy Wong .
In the memory of JUNG Woo-shik .